孩子 不懂生存规则就无法立足于世
I didn't get to where I am without knowing how the world works,son.
我明白这个道理
I understand that,Arthur.
而我 总能得到我想要的 干脆的说吧 到底是多少?
And I'm used to getting what I want,so why don't you just tell me what it'll take?
对不起...
I'm sorry.
别傻了 孩子 痛快点 告诉我标底
Don't prat about,son,just give us the bottom line.
我恐怕...
I'm afraid l...
我的主题公园 是英国北部地区中最大的一个
My theme park is the biggest in the North of England...
几乎是靠这双手建造起来的
most of it built with these hands.
5年之内 将会成为全欧洲最大的
In five years we'll be the biggest in Europe.
- 但是... - 没有"但是" 孩子
- Yes,but... - No buts,son.
告诉我 要赢得这次投标 得给你和Joe多少钱?
Just tell me what I have to give you and Joe 90 here to win that tender.
哦 很抱歉 标书都是保密的
I'm afraid the tenders are all sealed.
保密个鬼!Harry
Sealed,my ass.Harry.
这里有25,000
There's 25,000 there.
我不希望输给那些个 獐头鼠目的美国佬
I won't be beat by some bloody Yank dressed up as a mouse.
哇哦 那可是违规操作
Well,this is most irregular.
难道我们不是在做生意?
Are we doing business,or what?
象我常说的那样 我总是能得到我想要的
Like I said,I usually get what I want.
投标的截止日期一过
Once the deadline has passed...
我们就可以开始暗中操控了
we can get working on having it moved for you.
让那几个小毛孩输得体无完肤!
This will put us right up there with the big boys.
毋庸质疑!
I'm sure it will.
本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子 字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第1季第6集
S01E06 The Last Gamble
我想说 如果我是个女的 我会爱死我自己的
All I'm saying is,you know,if I was a bird,well,I'd shag me.
瞧你说的
Can you hear yourself?
我就说 她绝对是个同性恋 不是嘛?
I reckon she's gotta be a lesbian,ain't she?
就因为她让你吃瘪了?
Just because she knocked you back?
听着 伙计 我没有吃瘪 懂吗?
Listen,mate,I don't get knocked back,okay?
我说..她们不是同姓恋就是性冷淡
Unless they're either A:Lesbian,or B:Frigid.
- 或者 两者都是 - 没错
- Or both. - Exactly.
- 也许她有男朋友了? - 所以..?
- Maybe she's got a boyfriend. - So?
也许 他们相处的很好
Well,maybe she's happy with him.
拜托 相处的好又怎样?也许下一个会更好呢?
Mate,happy,so what?Why go for second best?
Mick 别考虑 回答我
Mick,straight off,okay?
如果你是个女人 你会不会追求我?
If you was a bird,would you shag me?
他的自信心刚刚受过挫 新来的前台小姐不吃他那套
He's having a crisis of confidence.The new receptionist blanked him.
很简单 会还是不会?
It's very simple.Yes or no?
不会
No.
好吧 因为你也是个同性恋
Well,that's because you'd be a lesbian.
Stacie 我们工作室怎么样了?
Stacie,what's our working capital like?
呃 还行 怎么啦?
Yeah,it's healthy.Why?
Albert找到目标了
Albert's got a bite.
Anthony Reeves
Sir Anthony Reeves.
今早之前 他还在某大型事业公司担任着CEO的职位
Until this morning,he was CEO of one of the major utility companies.
巨大的损失和过多的在建基础设施建设
Huge losses and under-investment in infrastructure...
导致公用事业费用提高了39%...
led to a rise in utility bills up to 39%..
他不得不引咎辞职
and calls for his resignation.
作为他无能及管理不善的"回报"
His reward for this inept piece of mismanagement...
他得到的是50万的解聘金
was a golden handshake of 500,000.
Anthony先生有很强的排外心理
Sir Anthony borders on the xenophobic.
一个顽固的英帝国拥戴者排斥所有来自欧洲的东西
Staunch defender of the pound,hates anything European.
年收入少于10万的人
He refers to anyone who earns less than 100,000 a year...
在他看来就是个"下里巴人"
as "a member of the great unwashed."
真特别
Nice man.
城里有套公寓 市郊还有间很不错的别墅
Apartment in the city and a rather nice country home...
他和妻子Janice及两条狗一同生活
which he shares with his wife Janice and two dogs.
怎么找到他的 Albert?
How did you find him,Albert?
我们是同一家俱乐部的会员
We're both members of the same gentleman's club.
过去一直是点头之交 最近我才了解到他的辉煌历史
We were on nodding terms until I learnt recently about his new fortune.
现在 你们成好朋友了?
So you became firm friends?
最好的朋友!
The best.
他还有两个不为人知的秘密 连他的妻子也不知道
And he has two dirty little secrets he hides from his wife.
对性的渴望
A hankering for prostitutes.
哦 不要啊!
No,please.
别担心 亲爱的...
Don't worry,my dear...
我觉得我们可以利用第二个
it's the second little vice I think we should use.
什么?
Which is?
我问他借阅报纸的时候发现的
I discovered it when I borrowed his newspaper.
他喜欢赌马
He likes the gee-gees.
不幸的是他的妻子非常反对赌博
Better still,his wife disapproves of gambling.
真是个调皮的孩子!
Who's a naughty boy then?
- 放长线 - 放长线?
- The wire. - The wire?
几乎没有人会放长线吊大鱼了
Nobody's worked the wire in 100 years.
最后一次看到 是在电影《骗中骗》里
Last time I saw that was in The Sting.
老把戏了 19世纪前使用的
It's an old-time scam,it's pre-1900.
跑马结果是由通过 美国的西方联合电报电话公司
Racing results used to go from east to west...
从东部传达到西部的
by Western Union telegraph.
你所需要做的就是 使人相信
All you had to do was convince the mark...
你能够在下注前 通过内部线报
that you had someone on the inside who could delay the results...
获悉比赛的结果
until you got the bet on.
Danny
Danny.
- 你在听吗? - 是的 Mickey
- Are you listening? - Yes,Mickey.
Ash 我们可以操作吗?
Ash,can we make it work?
可以 不过 现在大家都在看时实比赛
Yeah,but everyone watches races live these days.
- 是的 但不是在家看 - 是啊
- Yeah,but not in person. - No.
我想 原则上还是有机可趁的
The principle still holds good,I suppose.
用录象替代原来的信号就可以
Just have to use video link instead of telegraph.
Albert
Albert?
工程浩大
It's big.
我们也很优秀!
So are we.
有什么事?
What can I get you?
- 我在找个人 - 没找到吗?
- I'm looking for someone. - Aren't we all?
Danny Blue 你认识他吗?
Danny Blue.You know him?
不好意思 伙计 没听说过
Sorry,mate,never heard of him.
如果你有幸遇到这个人的话
On the off chance you meet him in the next few days...
可否替我把这个转交给他?
could you give him this for me?
当然 没问题 如果结果是4的话 你就得带我们参观伦敦了
Yeah,okay,if it said 4,I say you gave us a tour of London.
- 好的 谢了 - 不客气
- Yeah,thanks. - Yeah?Thank you.
你打赌又赢了
You've got a chip on your shoulder.
你该输一回 否则你总是自我感觉太好
You should lose it,or you'll always feel on the outside.
有必要吗?我一直都是很优秀的
What's new?I've been on the outside all my life.
在一个精英团队里 这种感觉会成为一种反作用
In a good crew,that will make you a liability.
- 我知道 - 那就好好处理
- I know that. - Then deal with it.
在这儿用午餐吗 Winstone先生?
Will you be lunching with us,Mr.Winstone?
不 谢谢 我和同事还有些事要谈
No,thank you,my colleague and I have some business to discuss.
- 图书馆正空着呢 - 太好了
- The library is free. - Lovely.
你怎么能记得住那么多不同的名字?
How do you remember all your names?
我不需要记住
I don't need to.
这样的地方 记住客人的名字 是他们的工作
In places like this,it's their job to remember them.
那是铁定赢的 James叔叔
This is a guaranteed winner,Uncle James.
你一定要相信我说的
You have just got to take my word on it.
我知道你说的没错 孩子 可是 我不喜欢赌博
I'm sure you're right,dear boy,but I'm afraid I don't gamble.
Anthony 还以为你躲起来了呢
Anthony,I thought you'd be in hiding.
真是无聊
Nasty business.
是那些无知大众的错
That's the problem with the great unwashed.
他们眼红那些赚大钱的人
They hate to see a fellow make a few pounds.
忘了介绍 Anthony 这是Peter 故友之子
I'm sorry,Anthony,this is Peter,the son of a very old friend of mine.
- 您好 先生 - 你好
- How do you do,sir? - How do you do?
Anthony最近被报社弄得焦头烂额
Anthony's having a bit of trouble with the press.
开玩笑 那帮市井之徒 不值一提
You're joking.They are scumbags,aren't they?
你也曾经遇到过麻烦?
You've had dealings with them?
我自己 没有 先生 几年前 我父亲有过类似经历
Not personally,sir.My dad did,a few years back.
他是个反欧洲运动的积极分子
He was an activist in the anti-Euro campaign.
- 媒体的焦点人物 - 是吗?
- Press were all over him. - Really?
行了 还是忘了吧 Peter Anthony 要一起聊聊吗?
Now,best forgotten,Peter.Anthony,won't you join us?
来 坐这儿吧 先生 我正要走
Here,take my seat,sir,I'm just off.
不用这么做
No need on my account.
不是的 事实上 我突然造访 是想给James叔叔一些内部消息
No,really,I only popped in here to make Uncle James a few quid.
不过 跟过去一样 他并不感兴趣
But as ever,he weren't interested.
人各有志 孩子 人各有志
Horses for courses,dear boy.
总之 下次再聊 很高兴认识您 先生
Anyway,we'll talk later.Nice to meet you,sir.
再见 James叔叔
Goodbye,Uncle James.
替我问候你的母亲
Say hello to your mother for me.
当然 我会的 再见!
I will,definitely.Bye-bye.
年轻的时候 被认为是个不肖之子
Black sheep of the family through his teens...
后来却浪子回头 是个非常不错的年轻人
but has turned out to be a rather nice young man.
他在投资公司吗?
He's in investments?
哦 不 跟马有关
God,no.Horses.
- 马? - 你知道 就是那种比赛之类的
- Horses? - You know,the racing variety.
有"小道消息" 或是 他们称为的那种消息
Had a "hot tip" or whatever it is they call it.
他有没有提过什么名字?
Did he mention the name?
- 名字? - 马的名字
- Name? - Of the horse.
哦 是的 说是...
Yes.It's...
哦 我忘了
No,it's gone.
要知道 Anthony 笨蛋是发不了大财的
But just as well,Anthony.A fool and his money are soon parted.
要咖啡吗?Paul!
Some coffee?Paul!
- 好了? - 是啊
- All right? - Yeah.
在这么漂亮的地方 和你这样的女孩一起 还真不错
What's a nice place like this doing with a girl like you?
- 希望一切都顺利 - 当然
- I take it it went well. - Yeah.
你得以我为傲 我是个很不错的成员
You'd have been proud of me.I was a real team player.
你真坦白 Danny
Your round,Danny.
你好 我想知道上一场是谁赢了?
Hello.I was wondering if you could tell me what won the last race?
随便哪个比赛
Anywhere.
很好 非常感谢
That's excellent.Thank you.
我听说你被某个女人拒绝了?
I heard you got blanked by some bird at the hotel.
我没有被拒绝好不好?她是个同性恋
I did not get blanked,okay?She's a lesbian.
是的 没错
Right.
早些时候 有个家伙来这儿找你
Had some bloke in here earlier,looking for you.
谁?
What bloke?
没留名字 不过他好象留了电话号码
He didn't leave his name,but he left his number here somewhere.
看上去有点道理啊 就是你说的
It seems it's true,what you say.
笨蛋是发不了财的
About a fool and his money.
这上面说有个家伙
There's a chap in here.
他被骗 据说是他竟然以为 自己买到了"伦敦眼"
He was apparently conned into believing he was buying the London Eye.
伦敦眼:世界最大的观景摩天轮
是吗?
Really?
显然他太想得到它了
Apparently turned up to take possession.
- 他到底在想什么? - 谁知道呢
- What was he thinking of? - I can't imagine.
谢谢!
Thank you.
问题是 有些人不该拥有那么多钱
Problem is,some people don't deserve money.
象我们这样的人 稍有点钱
When chaps like us earn a few bob...
就被说成中饱私囊
they call us fat cats.
象我 即使有人中了彩票 我也不会嫉妒的
I mean,I don't moan when one of the plebs wins the lottery,do I?
我就没你那么大度了
I could hardly put it better myself.
当然 希望他不会成为我的邻居
Providing he doesn't move in next to me,of course.
Margo's girl
Margo's Girl.
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
你刚刚问我马的名字 是Margo's Girl 下午1点的
That horse you asked me about,Margo's Girl,1:00 p.m.
突然间想起来了
It just came back to me.
哪场比赛 你知道吗?
Where was it running,do you know?
我不清楚
I have no idea.
我想知道它有没有赢?
I wonder if it won?
想知道结果 那很简单
It's easy enough to find out.
Paul 有匹马叫Margo's Girl 参加今天的某场比赛
Paul,there was a horse running today,Margo's Girl.
可以替我看看结果如何吗?
Could you see how it did for me,there's a good chap.
- 要是真赢了 你就该后悔了 - 我不沾赌的
- You'll be sick if it won. - I never gamble.
偶尔的一两次刺激 无伤大雅
There's nothing wrong with an occasional flutter.
我对赛马是一窍不通
I don't know one end of the horse from the other.
那可是"运动之王" 老伙计
It's the sport of kings,old chap.
看着你的马跑向Cheltenham的山顶
You haven't lived till you've seen your horse...
你才会觉得生活是如此有意义
running up that hill at Cheltenham.
我会记得你说的
I'll have to take your word for it.
Margo's Girl赢了 先生
Margo's Girl won,sir.
- 赔率? - 1赔12
- Price? - 12-to-1.
真不错
Good Lord.
你的这个故友之子 他到底是做什么的?
This nephew of yours,what does he do exactly?
说实话 我也不清楚 只知道是关于马的
Tell you the truth,I'm not sure.Just something to do with horses.
我很希望有机会再见见他
I'd very much like to meet him again.
行啊 我想没问题
Well,I'm sure that can be arranged.
你就是Danny
You must be Danny.
- 我不确信你会来 - 是的 我很好奇
- Wasn't sure you'd come. - Well,I was curious.
听着 伙计 我没时间 你是谁 找我干什么?
Listen,mate,I ain't got all day,so who are you and what do you want?
我叫Ray Fordham
The name's Ray Fordham.
你有他们说的那么厉害吗 Danny?
Are you as good as they say you are,Danny?
你到底是谁?警察?
What are you then?Cop?
我看上去象警察吗?
Do I look like a cop?
警察长什么样的都有 不是嘛?
Well,they come in all shapes and sizes,don't they?
我也是个骗子 和你一样
I'm a grifter,just like you.
是吗?我怎么从来没听说过?
Are you?How come I never heard of you then?
你听过苏格兰的Ray?
You have.Scottish Ray?
你就是苏格兰的Ray?你又不是苏格兰人
You're Scottish Ray?But you ain't even Scottish.
这个名字是出自我做的第一个大案
The name came from my first big con.
我用爱丁堡城堡的项目 骗了5万定金
I took a 50,000 down payment on Edinburgh Castle.
是的 我听说过
Yeah,I've heard about that.
是在94年?
'94,weren't it?
95年
'95.
又靠它的室内装饰项目 骗了2万
I took another 20,000 for putting in double-glazing.
你是不是很喜欢美国佬?
Don't you just love the Yanks?
是啊 他们天生爱冒险
Yes,they've got romance in their soul.
好的 很高兴认识你 Ray
All right,I'm glad to meet you,Ray.
我也是
Likewise.
我可以做什么 伙计?
So what can I do for you,mate?
我正在组个新队伍
I'm putting a new crew together.
是吗?不错 我认识不少人
Yeah?Well,I know some people.
我不要其他人 Danny 我要你
I don't want people,Danny.I want you.
好的 我想我们已经做得够多了 足够让他相信我们了
Well,I think we've hooked him in enough to give him a convincer.
Ash 你找到的地方如何?
Ash,what about this place you've found?
还行 需要再做些装修
Well,it has to be a build.
可以 弄得象样点 需要多久?
Okay,but let's make it good.How long?
几天吧 还要再找点帮手
Couple of days,if I can get enough bodies.
没问题 就这么做
Yeah,do it.
你半小时前就该来的
You should have been here half an hour ago.
抱歉
Sorry.
好的 后天Albert会安排 让他和Danny见一面
Right,Albert will set up the meet with Danny for the day after tomorrow.
- 你得准备好 - 我会的
- You have to be ready by then. - I will be.
Stacie 和Ash算下支出费用 后天你和Danny一起去
Stacie,work out the costs with Ash,then double up with Danny later on.
有问题吗?
Questions?
好的 开始行动
Okay,let's do it.
你有问题?
Problem?
没有
No.
我的朋友告诉我 你可以找到任何人
A friend of mine down here tells me you can find anyone.
只要你找的人还在伦敦 我就能找到他
If who you're looking for is in London,I can find them.
我要付多少钱?
How much is that going to cost me?
看你找谁...
Depends who it is...
找到之后打算怎么处置
and what you're going to do when you find them.
2个骗子 一个黑人 一个白人
Two con men,one black,one white.
我要杀了他们
I'm gonna kill them.
进展如何?
How's it going?
装饰很容易 不过我们需要搬些东西进来
Decoration's easy enough,but we need to start getting the hardware in.
什么东西?
What's the setup?
一些器材 适合那种半英里左右赛程的比赛
Five or six furlong races are the best bet.
这样 比赛会在1分钟或1分半钟内结束
Means the race is over in a minute to a minute-and-a-half.
- 很好 东西都准备好了吗? - 是的 该有的都有了
- Good.You've got everything you need? - Yeah.You'll know when I haven't.
嘿 小心点 这可是问Teddy借来的
Steady with those.Teddy wants them back.
James 见到你真高兴
James,what a lovely surprise.
这是Peter和他的朋友 Yvonne
This is Peter,and his young friend,Yvonne.
来吧 我给你们拿些饮料 Anthony在大厅
Come in,I'll fix you some drinks.Anthony's in the lounge.
- James 欢迎啊 - 谢谢!
- James,welcome. - Thank you.
- Peter 很高兴又见到你了 - 你好!
- Peter,nice to see you again. - Sir.
这位美女是....?
And who is this vision of beauty?
这是Yvonne
This is Yvonne.
认识你是我的荣幸 亲爱的
I'm delighted to make your acquaintance,my dear.
Anthony先生 您好
Sir Anthony.
不介意我借用一下这个年轻人吧?
Do you mind if I steal this young man?
当然不
Be my guest.
James告诉我 你很喜欢打赌
James tells me you're a betting man.
不完全是 先生
Not really,sir.
装聋作哑?来喝些东西 放松一下吧
Playing dumb?Lets see if a few drinks will loosen you up.
正是我想看到的
That's what I like to see.
鱼儿正在努力的自投罗网
A mark who does all the hard work himself.
好的 把电视接收器放在这里 以便我们实时接收比赛过程
Okay.We get the TV feed in here showing us the live race.
很明显 我们没办法控制比赛 他们是合法的
Obviously we can't fix the races,they're legit.
但是这个小家伙 可以接收到比赛前所有的图象
But this little baby holds up the pictures until the end of the race.
我们一知道谁获胜 就马上通知你
When we've got a winner,we'll give it to you.
在我们把图象信号传输到前厅之前
You've got two minutes to put a bet on...
你有2分钟时间下注
before we start feeding it through the front.
就所有人而言 他们是在看实况转播
As far as anyone is concerned,they're watching the race live.
2分钟时间并不长
Two minutes isn't very long.
再慢一点 我们的鱼儿就会有察觉了
You slow up the pictures any more,our man might smell a rat.
那也是逼不得已
It'll have to do.
好的主要区域已经布置好了
Right.The main area is fully functioning.
我从街灯上接了条线 作为我们的电力供应
I've tapped into a street light for electricity...
改了厕所的水流管道
re-routed mains water for the toilets.
只要他不踢墙....
As long as he doesn't kick the walls...
一切足够维持到任务结束
they should stay up long enough for the job.
完美的工作!
It's a work of art.
没错 我还找了20个小混混来做托
Yeah.I've got 20 grifters coming in as punters.
他们一来 这里就成"狼窝"了
When they're here,it will be the doggie's whatsits.
- 很好 明天我们就能开始 - 好的
- Okay,then we can start tomorrow. - Yeah.
我想说的是 你可以给我一些小道消息嘛
All I'm asking is that you throw the odd tip my way.
那超出了我的职权范围
It's more than my job's worth.
你告诉了James
You did it for James.
是的 但是他实质上就和家人一样 我的意思是 他能为我做任何事
Yeah,but he's virtually family.I mean,he'd do anything for me.
除了应有的尊重 先生 我几乎不了解你 是吧?
With all due respect,sir,I hardly even know you,do I?
James会为我担保的
James will vouch for me.
是吗?
Will he,now?
您是做什么?各种比赛 是吗?
So what are you?A racing man,are you?
我想 我该属于那种狂热的爱好者
I think I'm what you'd call an enthusiastic amateur.
听着 我要告诉你的事 不能让其他人知道
Listen,what I'm about to tell you mustn't go any further.
我保证!
You have my word.
我为syndicate工作
I work for a syndicate.
我们买比赛用的马
We buy racehorses.
我知道 你们有内部消息
I knew it.You've got inside knowledge.
有时候还不止这些
It's slightly more than that.
去年 我的东家和其他三家财团合作
Last year the company that I work for teamed up with three other syndicates.
去年 在Kempton 我们发现
Then at Kempton last year,we realized that between them...
他们拥有某一比赛中所有的马
they owned all the runners in a single race.
真的?
Really?
这样 他们所需要做的就是
From there it's just a short step to being able to determine...
决定哪一场次是哪匹马赢
which horses are going to win certain races.
你是说 暗箱操作?
You mean,fix them?
我没说是暗箱操作 我只是说 他们在比赛前就知道
I'm not saying fix them.I'm just saying they know who's going to win...
哪匹马会赢
before they start.
而你 可以知道获胜者的名字?
And you can get the names of the winning horses?
我?不 我只是个打工的
Me?No.I'm much too far down the food chain.
但是 你告诉过James马的名字
But the horse you told James about.
是的 我从Yvonne那儿知道的
Well,that came from Yvonne.
你的女朋友
Your girlfriend.
想知道原因吗?
Can I be honest with you?
- 当然 - 小声点
- Absolutely. - Come here.
听着 现在我完全信任你
Listen,I'm trusting you completely here.
我希望James叔叔没有看错你
I hope Uncle James ain't got you all wrong.
我保证 他没有
I can assure you he hasn't.
好吧 事实是...
Now,the truth is...
Yvonne和我不是真的在一起
Yvonne and me aren't really together.
她只是个高级公关 的确很吸引人
She's a high-class escort.Absolutely lovely.
我是说 每次我出席宴会都带着她
I mean,I take her out every now and again.
上周 我把她介绍给我的老板
Last week,I gave her number to my boss.
她和他在一起呆了会 并且偷听到他讲电话
She spends a bit of time with him.She overhears him talking on the phone.
现在 他已经对她完全着迷了
Now the thing is,he's got a bit of a crush on her.
他很想再见到她
So he wants to see her again.
可以理解
I don't blame him.
所以我在想 也许可以给更多人赚钱的机会
So,I gets to thinking maybe I can find out a few more winners.
我去找James叔叔 是因为 说实话 我没有足够的钱做本金
I went to Uncle James because,basically,I ain't got the funds to finance it.
所以 你打算找一个赞助者?
So you're looking for a backer?
当然 不然就不会跟你聊了
Well,we wouldn't be having this conversation if I weren't.
其实 上次我只筹到了1000块
I mean,the most I could raise last time was 1,000.
- 但是你赚了1万2 - 是的 没错
- But you got 12,000 back. - Well,yeah.
但是 假如我有1万的话呢?
But what if I had 10,000?
看上去 鱼儿已经咬钩了
Looks like we have a nibble.
我想 该对冰美人再次出击
I'm gonna have another crack at Frosty.
好吧 又得唠叨了
All right?Chatty as ever.
回见
See you.
嗨 不错的团队
Hey,that's quite a team.
Stacie Monroe Albert Stroller "三只脚"的Morgan...
Stacie Monroe,Albert Stroller,"Three Socks" Morgan...
还有 最厉害的Mickey Bricks
and the great Mickey Bricks.
你来这儿做什么?
What are you doing here?
我在想 你是否改变主意了
I just wondered if you'd made your mind up yet.
我们正在进行任务
We're in the middle of a score.
那么 你负责什么 Danny?
And what's your cut,Danny?
谁才是主角?
Who's calling the shots?
看看 你所做的就是 用你的天赋 为Mickey Bricks做嫁衣
See,all you're doing is using your talent to make Mickey Bricks look good.
扩大其声望
Big up his reputation.
我在跟他学习
I'm learning off him.
只要你在学 他就能一直拿你当猴耍
And as long as you're doing that,he'll treat you like a kid.
游戏该结束了 Danny
Clock's ticking,Danny.
没那么容易 我欠他们的
It ain't that easy.I owe them.
好吧 选择权在你 知道哪儿能找到我
Well,the choice is yours.You know where I am.
只有离开他们 你才能提升自己
You're never gonna move up in class,not until you break free.
准备好了?
All set?
你确定 下这些钱不会引起注意?
You're sure a bet of this size will go unnoticed?
听着 这是个私人的赛马俱乐部 有时候有的财团也会用
Listen,there's a private gambling club the syndicate uses sometimes.
我是那儿的会员
I'm a member there.
交易流量非常大
Strictly for high rollers.
我们用的是现金 绝对不会有问题
It's all cash,no questions asked.
我还曾经见过有人下注25万
I've seen people place bets of up to 250,000 there.
都没有人眨过一下眼
No one even bats an eyelid.
只要我们坚持一天只赌一次 没有人会注意我们的
If we stick to one bet a day,no one's gonna notice us.
我会把上次赢的钱都拿来下注
I'm going to put in all my winnings from last time.
全部12000块?
All 12,000?
都知道你不会输了 为什么不呢?
Why not,when you know you can't lose?
去哪儿?
Where to?
别担心
No worries.
好的 伙计们 车已经到了
Okay,guys.Car's pulled up.
好的 各位...
Okay,everyone...
演出开始!
showtime.
Stacie 回避一下
Stacie,out of sight.
这是我的会员卡
This is my card.
怎么会有这么个地方
You wouldn't even know this place was here.
这里仅供会员进入
It's strictly members only.
让我感觉离狗仔队远远的
It gets me away from the damn press.
这里还能玩轮盘赌和二十一点
We've got roulette and blackjack through there.
能想象嘛 2万块钱 一眨眼就没了
Can you believe it?20,000,beaten by a neck.
下次我该压只长颈鹿
Next time remind me to back a giraffe.
那是牌室
This is the poker room.
- Peter - Mike
- Peter. - Mike.
- 你好! - 好啊 很久不见了
- How you doing? - Hello.Long time no see.
见到你真高兴 还好吧?
Good seeing you.How you doing?
- 这是我的朋友Anthony Reeves - 很高兴有机会赢你的钱
- This is my guest Anthony Reeves. - It will be a pleasure to take your money.
恐怕今天不行 Mike 我们今天的运气很好
Not today,Mike.We're feeling very lucky.
是啊 在这里的每个人都这么认为
Yeah.You and everyone else in here.
那是Mike Taylor 这儿的经理
That's Mike Taylor,the manager.
他看上去十分的自信
He seems very full of himself.
是的 不过不会太久 不是吗?
Yeah,but not for long,right?
好的 Yvonne一旦知道名字 就会给我们打电话
Okay,Yvonne will call as soon as she gets the horse.
没多长时间比赛就会开始 所以一得到到消息
It's going to be close to the start,so you get your bet on...
你就得马上去下注
as soon as it comes through.
好的
All right.
这是我的那份
There's my money.
怎么样?
Well?
最后两个 赔率太高了
The last two,the odds are too high.
Stacie?
如果他们赢的太多 我们会提前收场
If they win too much it'll break us before we start.
1赔3或者再少点
Take 3-to-1 or less.
我们在看台上看到Flak Jacket正在通过
And on the stands,Flak Jacket coming through.
Flak Jacket在左侧要独自回家了
Flak Jacket coming home alone on the near side.
Flak Jacket越过了Sober Jones,在第三...
Flak Jacket gets up the wind from Sober Jones,in third...
Flak Jacket
Flak Jacket.
- 赔率? - 1赔2
- Price? - 2-to-1.
好了,开始
Okay,go.
- 你好 - 压Flak Jacket
- Hello.- Put it on Flak Jacket.
好的
Right.
5万,压Dancing Ridge下一场独赢
50,000.Dancing Ridge to win in the next.
5万压独赢.谢谢,先生
50,000 to win.Thank you,sir.
- 你的,先生 - 谢谢
- Here you are,sir. - Thank you.
2万4压下一场,Flak Jacket独赢
24,000 to win.Flak Jacket in the next race.
2万4压独赢.非常感谢
24,000 to win.Thank you very much.
这是你的赌注,先生,非常感谢
Here we are,sir,thank you very much.
它们准备好了.比赛开始
They're ready.That's it.And they're racing.
搞定了
They're off.
Flak Jacket,1赔2
Flak Jacket,2-to-1.
加油,小子,加油
Go on,son,come on.
放松些
Just relax.
加油,Flak Jacket
Come on,Flak Jacket.
加油,小子
Come on,son.
- 加快你的鞭子,孩子 - 他快了
- Get your whip out,boy. - He's coming.
就那样!去栏杆那里!
That's it!Go to the rail!
来吧,Flak Jacket!
Come on,Flak Jacket!
给它们瞧瞧.来吧
Show them the way.Come on.
来吧,我的小子!耶!
Come on,my son!Yes!
我告诉过你什么?
What did I tell you?
漂亮
Beautiful.
你这个美丽的小东西
You little beauty.
还没有确认,先生
It hasn't been confirmed yet,sir.
就是4万8千,再加上你的赌金 一共是7万2千
That's 48,000,plus your stake.That's 72,000 in all.
2万,3万,4万...
20,000,30,000,40,000...
5万,6万,7万 还有...
50,000,60,000,70,000 and...
2千.请拿好,先生
2,000.Here we are,sir.
你们最大的赌注是多少,伙计?
What's your maximum bet,mate?
- 我们没有最高限制,先生 - 谢谢
- We have no maximum,sir. - Thank you.
我们再来一次
Let's do it again.
不,一天一场,我们说好的
No,one race a day.We agreed.
- 再来一次不会有什么问题的 - 我们会引起别人的注意
- One more won't make any difference. - We'll draw attention to ourselves.
现在走吧,好吗?
Now let's just go,okay?
Flak Jacket
Flak Jacket.
我不能相信就这么简单
I can't believe it was that easy.
你不愿相信我拿到那匹马的名字都要作些什么
You wouldn't believe what I had to do to get that horse's name.
我不知道
I don't know.
可是告诉告诉我
Try me.
听着,事情是这样的 如果我们想真的赚大钱...
Listen,the thing is,if we want to make real money...
我们就必须在Yvonne还在里面的时候 堵上一笔大的
we need to put one big bet on while Yvonne's still on the inside.
那不急,是不是?
There's no rush,surely?
好吧,如果他打电话给中介要求换个女孩呢?
Well,what if he calls the agency and asks for another girl?
他一定是疯了
He'd be mad.
不,Yvonne是对的 我们不想冒这个险
No,Yvonne's right.We don't want to take that risk.
总之,当这一切都结束的时候...
And anyway,when all this is over...
你们这两个多情鹦鹉就可以一起去过周末了,不是吗?
you two lovebirds get to spend the week together,don't you?
- 就像我许诺过的,Tony - 的确是
- Just as promised,Tony. - So we do.
你怎么想?
So what do you think?
他还要来赌一次小的,确定一下
He wants one more smaller bet,just to make sure.
- 真是太好了! - 这不是Danny的错
- Wonderful! - It wasn't Danny's fault.
壶已经空了,我们付不出这个钱
The pot is empty,we can't pay out.
所有的准备都是要把他引进来 在下次下一把大的
Everything was geared to take him in for the big one next time.
- 他已经很近了 - 近但还没有下决心,Danny
- He's this close. - Close does not cut it,Danny.
没有用的.我们必须不能让他得逞
It can't be helped.We'll have to shut him out.
你知道,有时候,一个要求完美的请求...
You know,sometimes a desire for perfection...
会被误解成是批评
can be misinterpreted as criticism.
- 是那样吗? - 是的
- Is that so? - Yeah.
你怎么那么暴躁?
Why so grumpy?
我不知道
I don't know.
是Rachel的原因?
Is it Rachel?
我收到了最后的裁决
I had the decree nisi.
都结束了
It's all over.
你为什么不说出来?
Why didn't you say?
那又能有什么帮助?
How would that have helped?
可以提醒你这里的每个人都爱你
Could have reminded you that everyone here loves you.
或许这次以后,我们应该好好休息一下
Maybe after this one,we should take a break for a while.
我认为我们应该下5万
I think we should do 50,000.
随便你了
Whatever you say.
你好
Hello.
压Mostarsil
Put it on Mostarsil.
好了,在他到窗口之前就开始播吧
Run it now,before he gets to the window.
5万压Mostarsil在下一场独赢
Mostarsil in the next.50,000 to win.
比赛已经开始了,先生
The race has started,sir.
- 不会的,我是在它们开始之前说的 - 对不起,先生
- No,I said it before they started. - I'm sorry,sir.
有问题吗?
Problem?
- 我想要下注 - 比赛已经开始了,先生
- I was trying to place a bet. - The race has started,sir.
不能再下注,下次再试试吧
No more bets.Try the next race.
来吧,Mostarsil!
Come on,Mostarsil!
Christ!
- 1赔10,那可是50万啊! - 我没有下注
- 10-to-1,that's 500,000! - I didn't get the bet on.
- 什么? - 我没有来得及
- What? - I didn't have time.
那可是50万啊!
That's 500,000.
妈的!
Shit!
不,等等.我要看他们在做什么
No,wait.I want to see what they're doing.
好的,他准备要上钩了 我们已经为明天准备好了
Okay,so he's gone for the bait,and we're all set for tomorrow.
Stacie,Danny,把他卷进来吧
Stacie,Danny,go reel him in.
有什么意见吗?
Any thoughts?
你都已经全部掌握了
Think you've covered everything.
那就把他卷进来
Then go bring him in.
这次不能有错了
And no mistakes this time.
我知道,我知道,但我在教他
I know,but I'm teaching him.
你在窒息他
You're smothering him.
你要给他空间
Give him his head.
或许你会在他身上看见我所做的
Maybe you'll see in him what I did.
而我曾经在你身上见过一次
What I saw in you once.
我们有个问题,必须碰个面
We've got a problem,we're gonna have to meet up.
是的,好的.6点半怎么样?
Yeah,okay.What about 6:30?
好的,谢谢,Anthony
All right.Thanks,Anthony.
这个国家开始围捕法律了,你知道的
This country's got stalking laws,you know.
只是觉得我该让你知道我明天就要回去了
Just thought I'd let you know I'm heading back tomorrow.
3点会结账离开
I check out of the hotel at 3:00.
很好,但我还没有下决定
That's fine,but I haven't made a decision yet.
你会来的
You'll be there.
什么?
What?
有的财团开始被调查了
The syndicate's being investigated.
- 为什么? - 我不知道,好不好,但就是开始了
- Why? - I don't know,all right?It is.
有人听到了风声,都结束了
Someone got wind of it.It's all off.
- 不可能的 - 我告诉你了,就是
- It can't be. - I'm telling you,it is.
他们明天会做一笔,然后就开拔走人
They're gonna do one tomorrow,then pulling the plug.
等等,你是说他们会再做一次
Wait.You said they're doing one more.
已经布局好了
It's already set.
- 为什么我们不可以呢? - 你在说笑吗?
- Why can't we do it,too? - Are you having a laugh?
权威人士会像老鹰一样盯着整场比赛的
The authorities will be watching that race like hawks.
他们会盯着那些财团,而不是我们
They'll be watching the syndicate,not us.
我不知道.你在想什么?
I don't know.What do you think?
冒险
Risky.
他不敢,就这样
He who dares and all that.
确定这值得冒险吗?
Surely it's worth the risk?
如果我们要做这笔...
If we're gonna do this...
就应该是笔大的
it has got to be a big bet.
因为我告诉你了,这是最后的机会
Because I'm telling you,this is the last chance.
绝对
Absolutely.
我最多只能提升到3万
The most I can raise is probably going to be about 30,000.
开玩笑.我才不愿为这个而冒被抓住的危险呢
You've got to be joking.I'm not risking getting caught for that.
那要多少你才肯冒险?
So how much would it take?
50万
500,000.
- 什么? - 50万
- What? - 500,000.
即使只有1赔2的赔率,我们也能赚个100万
Even if we only get 2-to-1 again,we'd clear 1 million.
我怕这超出了我的范围
It's too rich for my blood I'm afraid.
如果有100万在银行的话,我们这个周末会非常美满的
We could have a wonderful week with 1 million in the bank.
对不起,不
I'm sorry,no.
好吧,如果你不能胜任...
Well,if you're not up to it...
这不是能不能胜任的问题...
It's not a question of not being up to it...
我只是不能一下子失去那么多钱
I just can't afford to lose that kind of money.
你怎么会失去呢?
How could you lose?
我是说,你都看见是如何运作的了
I mean,you've seen how it works.
即使这样
Even so.
50万
500,000.
这可是一生才一次的机会
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity.
我是说,要不就是现在,要不就是永远也没有了
I mean,it's now or it's never.
记住:"懦夫难得美人心"
Remember:"A faint heart never won a fair maiden."
好吧,我干了
Okay,I'm in.
银行经理觉得我有神经病 我只能威胁要关掉我的账户
Bank manager thought I was insane.I had to threaten to close my account.
你拿着双倍回来后他会冷静下来的
He'll calm down when you pay double back in.
你确信他们能接受这么大的赌注吗?
You're sure they'll take a bet this size?
你听到那个男人说的了,没有限制
You heard the man.No limit.
先生们.觉得运气不错吧?
Gentlemen.Feeling lucky again?
我认为没问题
I think we'll be okay.
是吗?
Think so?
我真是希望里面都是钱
I do hope that's full of money.
我们很快就能把这笑容从他脸上擦掉
We'll soon wipe that smile off his face.
不要理他
Just ignore him.
Yvonne会通过电话告诉是哪匹马 然后和我们在这里碰面
Yvonne will phone the horse through,and then she'll meet us here.
我去拿点喝的
I'll get us a drink.
- 有结果了吗? - 幸运儿最后会赢
- Anything? - Favorite won the last.
- 我们要试图取得更大的几率 - 等等
- We've gotta try and get bigger odds. - Wait.
...Kieren Fallon在Roofer和Dennis El Menace的前二,三位...
...Kieren Fallon has gone two or three in front of Roofer and Dennis El Menace...
战争会在...
battling on...
明白了
Got it.
下一场把所有的都压在Roofer上
Place it all on Roofer in the next race.
好的,我们到时候见
Yeah,I'll see you there.
Roofer
Roofer.
1赔8.那可是4百万!
8-to-1.That's 4 million!
他们都在围栏里.去押注吧!
They're in the stalls.Get the bets on!
最后一场即将开始
Last one to go on the inside.
你的
Here you go.
下一场Roofer
Roofer in the next race.
50万镑押独赢
500,000 pounds to win.
- 有问题吗? - 稍等,先生
- Is there a problem? - One moment,sir.
怎么了,Paul?
What's wrong,Paul?
这位先生要下一份大注,先生
This gentleman wants to place a large bet,sir.
多大?
How large?
50万
500,000.
- 赔率? - Roofer.1赔8
- Price? - Roofer.8-to-1.
我明白这里是没有上限的
I understood there was no limit.
- 接受这位先生的赌注 - 但我没有时间来数
- Take the gentleman's bet. - I haven't got time to count it.
拿着箱子.如果他的马赢了,我们再来数...
Take the case.If the horse wins,we'll count it...
然后把这里的所有都付给他
and pay out on whatever's there.
谢谢,先生
Thank you,sir.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
- 好了 - 是的
- That's it. - Yes.
那么,你们都搞定了吗?
So,you get it on all right?
Roofer,50万押它独赢
Roofer,500,000 to win.
独赢?我告诉你"前两名"
To win?I told you "place."
- 什么? - 我是说"前两名"
- What? - I said "place."
财团主张前两名会让所有人都看不破伪装
The syndicate went for a place to throw everyone off the scent.
那才是我告诉你的 我说了,"Roffer在前两名"
That's what I told you.I said,"Place it on Roofer."
赛马已经结束三分之一赛程了
That horse finishes third.
弄错了.我想要回我的钱
There's been a mistake.I want my money back.
- 先生? - 我是想说"前两名"不是"独赢
- Sir? - I meant to say "place," not "win."
比赛已经开始了,先生
The race has started,sir.
我不管,我要要回我的钱!
I don't care,I want my money back!
- 赌马规则规定... - 把我的钱给我
- House rules dictate that... - Give me my money.
拜托,放松
Come on,take it easy.
这里发生了什么事情?
What the hell is going on?
你不明白.搞错了
You don't understand.There's been a mistake.
没有弄错,先生,你的马刚输了
There was no mistake,sir.Your horse just lost.
放开我!
Get off me!
你不是Anthony Reeves先生吗 伙计们,来点镜头
Aren't you Sir Anthony Reeves?Boys,get some shots.
这就是你用辉煌的握手来做的事情吗,先生?
This is what you're doing with your golden handshake,sir?
用纳税人的钱来赌博?
Gambling with the taxpayers' money?
我没有赌博,我不赌博的
I'm not betting,I don't gamble.
- 这个男人在你这里下了赌注了吗,先生? - 这是机密
- Did this man place a bet with you,sir? - That's confidential.
你能否向我们的读者解释一下 为什么你会出现在这个私人的赌博俱乐部的,先生?
Can you explain to our readers why you're in a private gambling club,sir?
我在拜访一个朋友
I'm visiting a friend.
你觉得纳税人应该资助你的赌博 喜好是否公平?
Do you think it's fair that the taxpayers should fund your gambling habit?
来吧,先生,你有什么要对我们的读者说的吗?
Come on,sir,what have you got to say to our readers?
比纳税人更重要吗,先生?
More important to the taxpayer,sir?
这是辆好车.你也是用你的所得来供车的吗,先生?
It's a nice car.Did you fund that out of your winnings,sir?
都在这里
There it is.
干得好,大家辛苦了 好了,让我们离开这里
Well done,everyone.All right,let's get out of here.
明天在Eddie的酒吧把工钱给你们.现在走吧
Wages in Eddie's Bar tomorrow night.Let's go.
- 做得好,伙计 - 好了,伙计们
- Well done,mate. - All right,mate.
现在一切都结束了 我有一些事情必须告诉你
Now this is all over,there's something I need to tell you.
事情是...
The thing is...
看看你们.就像下水道中的老鼠
Look at you.Rats in a sewer.
视力不错吧?这是什么?激光?我听说它们很不错
Eyesight better?What was it?Laser?I hear they're very good.
我们能为你做什么,Arthur?
What can we do for you,Arthur?
你能为我做什么?
What can you do for me?
你可以考虑跪下来亲我的脚...
You could try dropping to your knees,kissing my feet...
求我不要把这墙的痛苦加诸在你身上
and begging me not to paint the walls with you.
但我还是会满足你上次的嘴脸
But I'll settle for what you've just taken off the last mug.
对不起,我不知道你在说什么
I'm sorry,I don't know what you're talking about.
你们只有10秒时间
You've got 10 seconds.
把钱给他,Danny
Give him the money,Danny.
- 等等 - 闭嘴
- Hold on a minute. - Shut up.
不
No.
我恨透了他一直来告诉我 我什么时候可以说话,什么时候不可以
I'm sick of him telling me when I can speak and when I can't.
- 我来处理这个 - 就像你处理所有的事情一样?
- I'll handle this. - Like you do with everything?
对不起,Mickey,除非我错过了点什么...
I'm sorry,Mickey,but unless I've missed something here...
你带我们进入了洪流中,却忘记带划水的浆
you've just led us up shit creek and forgot to pack the paddles.
哦,所以你才会那么做,是不是,Danny?
And that's what this is all about,isn't it,Danny?
因为你觉得你会做得更好
'Cause you think you could do better.
你为了避免出差错而做的所有事情就是低估我
Everything you've done since you got out of nick has been down to me.
低估你?
Down to you?
除了那句印象深刻的鹦鹉学舌:你自己来解决它们
Except for the parrot impressions:You do them yourself.
你是个弱智的骗子艺术家,Danny...
You were a short con artist,Danny...
在俱乐部酒吧骗骗那些喝醉的人 直到我把你带进来
working the clubs and bars for drinks till I took you in.
是啊,是你给我的机会,我很感激...
Yeah,you gave me a shot,and I'm grateful for that...
但那以后我一直在支持你
but I've been carrying you ever since.
不,你唯一支持的只是过于膨胀的自信心
No,the only thing you've been carrying is an over-inflated ego.
你不应该这么说自己,小子 你的确有一些含量
You shouldn't be so hard on yourself,son.You do have some qualities.
就这样了?
Is that it?
就这样,嗯,Mick?
That's it,huh,Mick?
你所有问题的答案
The answer to all your problems.
事情没有按你的方向来发展
Things ain't going quite your way,take a swing.
你就严厉斥责
Lash out.
你搞砸了
You screwed up.
现在把这个男人的钱还给他 然后走吧
Now give the man his money back and move on.
我本来就打算那么做的
I was gonna do it when you started this.
你是要把这箱可笑的钱给他
You were going to give him the case of funny money.
他就是这么要求的
It's what he asked for.
如果他发现这堆现金只是堆废纸要多久?
And how long would it take him to realize this cash is crap...
多久他就能回来杀了我们?
come back here and kill us?
做得好.你真是聪明.如果你不告诉他的话 他可并不知道这是箱假钞,你个天才
Well done.Brilliant.He didn't know it was fake until you just told him,genius.
你以为他不会发现吗?
You don't think he's gonna find out?
这东西,伙计,不能在任何街角的商店里面使用!
This stuff,mate,wouldn't pass in a corner shop!
那你要怎么做?把我们的钱给他?
So what would you do?Give him our money?
如果只有把钱给他和死亡两种选择呢?当然是把钱给他!
If it's a straight choice between that and death?Yes!
那会让我们一无所有
That would clean us out.
Mickey,他可拿着把猎枪!
Mickey,he's holding a shotgun!
我们会一无所有的!
We'd have nothing!
好吧,如果你要为了这个而G了性命...
Fine.If you wanna get killed,for what...
6万,还是7万?那就随便吧
60,000,70,000,go ahead.
给钱,Mick
Do it,Mick.
在你生命中,做一件正确的事情
For once in your life,do the right thing.
你到底怎么了?
What happened to you?
抽屉里有多少,Ash?
What's in the drawer,Ash?
就像你说的,6万,7万最多了
Like you said,60,000,70,000,tops.
付给那个人
Pay the man.
我想你最好按那个年轻人说的做
I suggest you do what the young man says.
确定那里面没有这些可笑的钱
And make sure there's none of that funny money in there.
对不起,Mick
I'm sorry,Mick.
4天内有5万镑的利息,不错啊
50,000 profit in four days,not bad.
就像我告诉过你的,我总是能得到我要的
Like I told you boys,I usually get what I want.
你感觉到了吗?
Did you feel it?
太惊人了
Amazing.
- 我在滴... - 对不起
- I'm dripping... - I'm sorry.
接受你的复仇
Taking your revenge.
好了,来吧,大伙儿 我们现在马上离开!
All right,come on,everybody,let's get out of here now!
你今天过得如何,亲爱的?
Did you have a good day,dear?
Conmen,我的助手,他们以为在和一个该死的白痴打交道
Conmen,my ass.They thought they were dealing with a bloody idiot.
这些北部的乡村小子,还嫩着呢
Some country boy from up north,still wet behind the ears.
他们不会再犯那种错误了
They won't make that mistake again.
多带几捆苏格兰南部的小妞再来打败我吧
Take more than a bunch of Southern Jessies to get the better of me.
你还好吗,老板?
You all right,boss?
好了,就等一会儿
Right.Just wait a second.
等等
Wait.
我要走了,我以后不会再纠缠着你
I'm going now,so I won't be pestering you anymore.
好了,是这样的.我猜我非常想知道...
Okay,that's it.So I guess what I really wanted to know is...
为什么你不愿意和我一起出去?
why you wouldn't go out with me.
因为你是个女同性恋.是了!没有什么问题了
'Cause you're a lesbian.Yes!There's nothing wrong with that.
我就该死的知道
I bloody knew it.
- 不 - 是的,绝对是
- No. - Yes.Absolutely,yeah.
- Danny,你要跟我谈谈 - 什么时候?
- Danny,you wanted to talk to me. - When?
在Arthur进来之前你说有些事情必须要和我说
Before Arthur came in you said there was something you had to say.
哦,那个,没事了
Oh,that.It was nothing.
- 肯定? - 当然
- Sure? - Positive.
我以为你准备告诉我 你要加入苏格兰的Ray的队伍呢
Only I thought you were going to tell me you were joining Scottish Ray's new crew.
- 你知道? - 我知道所有的事情
- You knew that? - I know everything.
- 你们两个还要争论不休吗? - 是时候走了
- Are you two still squabbling? - Time to go.
- 我们要离开一会儿了 - 适当的休息一段时间
- We'll be gone for a while. - Have a well-earned rest.
- 但我们知道你在想什么 - 市场上会出现空挡了
- But we know what you're thinking. - Gap in the market.
- 想试试你的运气吗? - 你知道如何做就很简单
- Think you might try your luck? - Easy when you know how.
但如果你要做的话...
But if you do...
你必须记住骗子的首要规则
You gotta remember the first rule of the con.
你永远不能骗到一个正直的人
You can't cheat an honest man.
- 不会发生 - 不可能
- Can't happen. - Impossible.
找某些想要不劳而获的人
Find someone who wants something for nothing.
应该不会太难
Which shouldn't be hard.
然后让他们偷鸡不着蚀把米
And then give them nothing for something.
谢谢,船长
Thank you,Captain.
你知道,我一直在想
You know,I've been thinking.
我不再年轻了
I'm not getting any younger.
或许我应该退休.从容地鞠躬谢幕
Maybe I should retire.Bow out gracefully.
- 你是认真的? - 绝对
- You're serious? - Absolutely.
- 这可要让人号啕大哭了,Albert - 你们会找到其他人的
- It'd be a crying shame,Albert. - You'll find someone else.
没人会像你一样,Albert
There's no one quite like you,Albert.
Albert,这是你的选择.不管你怎么决定
Albert,it's your choice.Whatever you decide.
谢谢,Michael
Thank you,Michael.
...所以我对这个家伙说,"你疯了
...so I said to this guy,"You're crazy.
"我的老家伙留给了我3百万...
"My old man leaves me $3 million...
"我都要用来投资糖蜜吗?"
"and I'm going to invest in molasses?"
我告诉他了.我说"我并不是除了鞋子什么都不知道"
I told him.I said,"I don't know nothing about shoes."
你要我帮你拿饮料吗,Albie?
Do you want me to hold your drink for you,Albie?